Our baby is a woman now.
Yeah. I know. honey.
I-I don't have time for all that today.
- Bye.
- Have fun at your little camp.
My little dove is flying away.
I got my dorm assignment today.
And I met my roommate.
You know. I don't feel like we're a match.
See. when my daughter has
a problem. I have a problem.
When I have a problem.
everyone in the path of my solution
has a bigger fucking problem.
- You're trespassing.
Cooper!
Stop! You're killing him!
I'm gonna call Odessa pd.
I understand it now. what drove him.
There's a rush. an
exhilaration to the risk.
He died because of it. cami.
President of my company can't be averse
to the very thing that built it.
What are you saying?
I'm saying you're fired.
It is gonna be a scorcher.
Hundred and nine.
Yeah. in the shade. no less.
"Surface of the sun" hot.
"Fry an egg on the pavement" hot.
Hotter than a two-dollar...
whoa. whoa. whoa.
This is a family show.
Bicycle.
That is one hot bike.
Stolen. I say.
We need some "cool me down" music.
And a "tall drink of water" tune.
Play it.
Pop.
You're in my chair.
Well. actually. it's my chair.
So are the rest of 'em.
Well. I take that back.
Technically. this chair belongs
to my ex-wife's ex-husband.
just like every other stick of
furniture in that fucking house.
It's too early in the
morning to contemplate
what the fuck that means.
You're up early.
Yeah.
I got fired yesterday.
For what?
For trying to run the
company like a business
instead of a memento or a dream
or whatever the hell motivates her.
What are you gonna do?
Well. got a meeting with
the president of chevron
this afternoon.
So. finding another ship to
jump on ain't the problem.
What's the problem?
Not sure I want to jump
on somebody else's ship.
- There another option?
- Yeah.
Do what I used to do.
Hunting leases. Be a land man.
Tell you the truth. I don't know
if I have the energy for it anymore.
I damn sure don't have the savings.
Too damn old to be
chasing my tail around.
You haven't saved enough to retire?
You know my wife.
- Ex-wife. last I checked.
- Yeah.
- Hey. Dale.
- Fellas.
You know. I can make some calls.
- You know. get the word out.
- Well. trust me. bud.
- the word's out.
- Yeah.
What do you got today?
I'm just prepping the next
work over at your son's field.
That's it.
Unless you tell me to walk.
I go where you go. Tommy.
I appreciate that. buddy. Thank you.
Yes. sir.
Well. if that don't warm your toes...
A little loyalty left in the world.
Well. shit. we been
together. what. 20 years?
Right at it. Yeah.
And besides. m-Tex.
they wouldn't last a year without him.
Fucking Mark my words.
No. sir.
Hey. Nate.
I'm gonna talk to her.
Tommy. It was an emotional...
is the buyout on
Cooper's leases executed?
Well. soon as you sign it.
or I guess cami needs to sign it now.
Give it to me. Give me the contract.
I'm not sure I can do that.
Nate. cami didn't negotiate it. I did.
She has absolutely no fucking
knowledge of that transaction.
We've already paid the
money on his behalf. Tommy.
You drafted that agreement. right?
- 'Cause you asked me to.
- Exactly.
And I presented it to a 22-year-old kid
without presence of legal counsel.
He had absolutely no fucking
legal guidance whatsoever.
Now. if that's not the very definition
of "diminished capacity."
I don't know what is.
Well. he still initiated a drill crew
by falsely representing himself
as a representative of our company.
There are extreme civil and
criminal consequences to that.
Just give me the day. Nate.
Give me the day. and I will
hand you a check or the contract.
I mean. if I hadn't earned
your trust by now... God.
Morning.
You have got to be shitting me.
You're the one that said "hand job."
Hey. pop?
Can I grab coffee?
By all means.
Is there something you
forgot to tell me about?
Nothing comes to mind.
How about a five-foot-three blonde
with an ass like a breadbasket?
Yeah. She spent the night.
The battery died in her car.
and we needed jumper cables
and a truck to jump it with.
I got both.
All right.
What else did she do?
Number one. it's none
of your fucking business.
And number two...
Number two is none
of your business either.
Are you fucking with me?
Her car battery died. Tommy.
We slept. That's all we did.
And I got to hold a
beautiful woman in my arms
for the first time in 50 fucking years.
and I'll tell you something. son.
today. I feel better
than I've felt in decades.
So. I would appreciate it
if you would not fuck
that feeling up for me.
Yeah. well. when you
snuggle up to a good one.
it does have restorative effects.
Good for the body. good for the soul.
- good for everything.
- Yeah.
Well. I think we finally found
something we agree on 100%. pop.
What's wrong with you?
You still not used to seeing
girls run around in their underwear?
Cami called.
She wants me in fort worth.
I guess I'm next.
She ain't gonna fire you.
She could do that over the phone.
What. then? In 11 years.
monty never called
me to fort worth once.
Well. it's my guess that she's
gonna make you president.
At least for now.
I don't know why it didn't start.
Car's brand-new.
You got a cell phone booster in it?
Yeah. that's probably it.
They probably didn't
wire it through the ignition.
so it just keeps running
even when the car ain't.
- Hey. Dale.
- Yeah?
Hey. stand down on Cooper's field.
Stand down?
Yeah. Don't drill. Don't
build a pad. Don't do anything.
Don't do anything. Got it. Yes. sir.
- All right.
- Okay.
Hey. hon. you might want
to put some britches on.
You're driving half the
neighborhood crazy.
and you're getting the other half
- in a shitload of trouble.
- Fuck 'em.
She don't want him staring.
she should give him
something to stare at.
Good lord. I'll tell you what. bud.
Whoever catches that one's gonna have
a hell of a time holding on.
Sure as shit hope it ain't
my 82-year-old father.
Yeah. good luck with that.
- Yeah. You got it.
- I'll see you. bud.
Okay. let's get this sucker running.
I'm-a show you how to burn out in it. too.
What?
Just enjoying the view.
You want some breakfast?
- No.
- Gracias. mi amor.
De nada.
I'm seeing your friend's wife for brunch.
Which friend?
The oil man in the cowboy hat.
- Tommy?
- Yeah.
Interesting.
Not so interesting.
Her daughter is going to tcu now.
and doesn't have any friends here.
But... She has one now.
- Bella.
- Yeah?
Make sure you answer
questions with questions.
I know the game. Do
you think he told her?
That should be the
first question you ask.
Fuck.
Put this on your eye.
I hurt in places I didn't even know he hit.
Made you breakfast.
No. I don't think I can chew.
Well. that's why I made oatmeal.
Here you go.
You put berries in it.
Honey. too.
This is a very "white boy" breakfast.
No. that's a "I just fought for my life"
"and I need carbs and
vitamins to heal" breakfast.
We need to have a conversation.
We're getting married. right?
Yeah.
And-and you've been married before.
Where you going with this. Cooper?
You didn't have a job
when you were with elvio.
And if you want to work. that-that's fine.
I'm... I'm just asking...
I'm begging. please don't work there.
You don't have to worry
about that anymore.
Look. if you wake up
with some new passion
or invent a better light bulb
or-or just find something you want to do.
I'm-I'm your number one supporter.
Don't worry about the
phone bill and the mortgage.
Just leave that to me.
It's not important.
He's important.
You're important.
You're... you're everything to me. I...
I don't want to go to the police station.
Hey.
We have to file formal charges
against the son of a bitch.
or he'll do it again.
After what you did to him.
I don't think he's gonna do it again.
He won't do it to you
again. but he'll do it again.
It's-it's just what he is.
Yeah. you're right.
Let's get this over with.
You spend more time with
your abuelita than you do me.
That's what we're gonna fix.
- Yes. sir?
- You still in midland?
Yes. sir. About to take off now.
Okay. well. wait 15
minutes. I'm on my way.
Got it.
Hey. Tommy.
Hey. Bob. You in Houston?
Walking into a meeting
in Dallas. actually.
Okay. can you squeeze
another one in? It's worth it.
Well. that has me curious.
My lunch is free.
All right. I'll take it.
Mister Charles. say 12:30?
Only if you let me pay.
Not a chance. See you then.
All right. bud. I'll see you there.
Hey.
Ever heard the saying "to
be early is to be on time.
and to be on time is to be late"?
I haven't. but I get the gist.
Sorry. I'll be early tomorrow.
That's what I like to hear.
No excuses. just fix the problem.
Go and get stretched out.
All right. ladies.
gentlemen. Jogs to sprints.
Forty meters for the jog.
40 meters for the sprint.
All right. let's go. Groups of six.
Group one. go.
Group two. go.
Group three. let's go.
We got some slackers on the form.
Keep that heart rate up.
I want you speed walking.
This is not a vacation.
Group one. let's go.
Group two. get ready. let's go.
Group three. let's go.
Hadley. catch up. Thank you.
We never worked out like this at aledo.
This isn't the workout.
This is the warm-up.
- This is the warm-up?
- Yeah.
Weight train three days a
week. Today. it's plyometrics.
Lunge. box jump. core work...
- When do we learn the cheers?
- We work on cheers every day.
Look. high school this ain't. really.
Almost killed me my freshman year.
but you'll get used to it.
All right. we're gonna lunge for 40.
and we're gonna walk for 40.
Knees behind ankles. let's go.
Come up a little slower than that.
Keep going. Group two. let's go.
In unison. please.
That means at the same time.
Group three. can you
do better than group two?
Let's hope so. Let's go.
- Go. go. go. go.
- You see blondie?
Blondie in line two?
Her ankles ain't strong enough yet.
Push it back.
You see. she's got to keep
cocking her feet like 45 degrees off?
Yeah.
All right. everybody. Gather in a circle.
We're gonna do some
floor work. Let's go. let's go.
All right. everybody. go grab some water.
Gonna line up for box jumps.
I'm gonna need Kennedy.
Sophia. Miller. Evan. Jack. blue.
Norris? Norris?
Ainsley Norris?
Have a seat on the bench.
For what?
Just put your feet up. It's your ankles.
You have to strengthen the ligaments
and the muscles in your ankle.
You won't last a week if you don't.
Can I strengthen them in a week?
It'll take six weeks or
more to make a difference.
so I'm gonna wrap 'em for now.
And I'll write out a workout regimen.
give it to the strength coach.
Do it at the end of your
workout. not the beginning.
I don't want your ankles
fatigued before you lift weights
or practice routines. okay?
Okay.
Meet us ten minutes before practice.
and we'll get you wrapped.
She already get hurt?
It's preventative. coach.
Just need to get her ankles stronger.
All right. let's walk her
through it after practice.
Dope.
Drink a lot of water today. okay?
You're in shape. but you're
not in this kind of shape.
Stay hydrated.
Thank you.
Not sure you should be
using the plane. Tommy.
Well. it's flying a dead leg.
It's going to fort worth
whether I'm on it or not.
Looks like you're going.
too. Can I bum a ride?
Sure.
You know the drill. Quick 30 minutes.
- You got vehicles waiting?
- Yeah.
Can you do me a favor and.
call ahead. set me a rental car?
Thanks. bud.
You know. I don't think she'll
make me president. Tommy.
Perhaps seeking advice
on finding a new one.
What I will say is.
letting you go is a huge mistake
that she should reconsider.
I don't know. Nate.
I'm kind of thinking of it as fate.
I got a pretty good idea.
I don't get many of those.
so I'm gonna chase it.
Care to share this idea?
Not yet. but it's coming
your way. I promise.
So. he grabbed you.
threw you to the ground. then hit you.
Grabbed me. and I fought.
Fought how?
Punched. scratched. anything I could do.
I can't remember if he hit me
and then threw me on the ground
or the other way around.
I know he hit me when
I was on the ground.
with a rock or something.
Can I get you to just
lift this up. just a little bit?
Just for a minute.
Yeah. thank you.
Turn around.
Mr. Norris?
- Yeah?
- Can we have a word?
Just want to clear up some
of the details from last night.
Sure.
Go ahead and have a seat right there.
Can we get you a coffee or anything?
- No. I'm fine. Thank you.
- All right. so.
walk us through your
recollection of what happened.
Okay. I went to see my fiancée at work.
Her boss said she
was on a break outside.
When I went outside. I
found a man on top of her.
pulling her pants down. and
she was. she was pretty beat-up.
And you know that how?
'Cause of the blood on her face
and the fact she was
unconscious when I found her.
Okay. Then what?
And. put him in a rear choke.
pulled him off of her.
flipped him to the ground.
and punched him in the face.
And her boss and the bouncers
held him till you guys got there.
And how many times
would you say you hit him?
- I don't know.
- Guess.
Less than five? More than five?
I-I really don't know.
It all happened so fast.
How about 17?
You hit him 17 times. Mr. Norris.
If I don't know that. how do you know it?
We counted.
Security camera in the alley.
So. what are you
saying? If it was your wife.
you would've done something different?
If it had been my wife.
I would've shot him.
And that would be actively defending her.
Seventeen punches to the face.
he was no longer a threat. Mr. Norris.
- Excuse me...
- Yeah?
How much longer do
they need my fiancé?
- I-I'll ask.
- Thank you.
Yeah.
Yeah?
Hey. the. victim looks
pretty ready to leave.
We're gonna be a while.
Okay.
Did you. did you ride with your fiancé?
I did.
We can arrange for
someone to take you back.
They're gonna be a while. I think.
Why a while?
I don't know. ma'am. It's not my case.
I'm just gonna wait.
- Okay. Yeah.
- Thank you.
Sir. you can take a seat right here.
The detective will be
with you in a second.
Yeah.
Hey. They're holding Cooper in a room.
and it's taking forever.
Shit.
Ariana. that guy died.
Look. if you know a good
lawyer. you call him up.
Yeah.
Hello?
Hey. this is Ariana Medina.
I don't know if you remember
me. I'm elvio's. widow.
I remember you.
- I need your help.
- My help?
Okay. perhaps you don't
recall our last interaction?
A man tried to rape me last night.
Cooper... you remember Cooper.
Y-Yes. I remember Cooper.
He pulled him off me
and fought him. Beat him.
The man died. and the police
are holding him in a room.
Okay. okay. hold on. Slow down.
Go back to rape. Explain.
I was on a break from work.
Went outside for some fresh
air. and a customer that I was
having problems with in the past.
he was waiting for me.
Cornered me. threw me on the ground.
Okay. I got it.
Rebecca. Cooper saved my life.
Yeah. He has a habit
of doing that. it seems.
Pretty good habit.
So detectives have him
in an interview room?
Yeah.
Okay. put me on speaker.
I need you to walk into
that room. do not knock.
tell Cooper to stop talking.
Set the phone on the table. Go. now.
Okay.
Whoa. m-miss. you
can't be in here. Hold on.
- Hold on.
- Stop talking. Not another word.
This is Mr. Norris's attorney.
the one you failed to notify
before questioning my client.
Cooper. did they
explain your rights to you?
They ain't explained nothing to me.
Well. at this point. gentlemen.
anything he says and
anything he has already said
is inadmissible in court.
I'm 15 minutes away.
I'll be there in seven.
Which interview room?
- Four.
- On my way.
You know who calls lawyers. Cooper?
Guilty men call lawyers.
I called the lawyer.
What am I guilty of?
How you look your wives
in the eyes after all this.
no idea.
Call Tommy Norris.
Thank you.
Yeah?
Whatever favors you have with
law enforcement in this county.
you need to call them in.
They're gonna hang a
murder charge on your son.
The hell did... did you say "murder"?
Who the fuck did he murder?
According to last night's police blotter.
a 59-year-old white male
named Jonathon reasner.
And who in the fuck is that?
I'm playing catch-up. too.
Apparently. he sexually
assaulted the girlfriend.
I'm on my way to Odessa pd now.
Any reinforcements
you can send my way
would be greatly appreciated.
Yeah. okay. well. you
just get the lay of the land
and call me back. all right?
- I will.
- All right.
- Tommy?
- Walt.
what in the shit is going on with my son?
I just heard about it.
Well. you're gonna have
to help me fix it. okay?
This old boy died. Tommy.
I don't give a shit.
I need the facts. Walt.
I need the facts. I need police
reports. I need everything.
Every goddamn thing. so get on it.
Heading that way now.
Can you give me a fucking chance?
Bella.
Ciao.
- My god. your dress.
- Bella. Mwah.
Hi.
Isn't this just the cutest place?
I love it. It's my favorite in fort worth.
And this reminds me of soho.
- London?
- Yeah. Okay. food.
There is nobody in the U.S.
that can make a beef Wellington
even edible. but here is mamma Mia...
Come on. girl. That's
a little heavy for me.
I am currently winning
the war against my hips.
and I refuse to give
them any ammunition.
Please.
Okay. then order the
blue crab pot pie. Beautiful.
All right.
- This is so fun.
- It is.
- I love it.
- Yeah.
- Is Tommy in town?
- He's in midland.
I think. I mean. you know. Tommy
runs around like a scalded dog.
You never know where he is.
Okay. I-I assumed he would
be here taking meetings. though.
He takes his share.
What?
It-it-it's... not my place.
I mean. secrets is no
way to start a friendship.
He was fired.
Yesterday. at the river.
Or-or at least that's what cami
told Danny anyways.
that they have different
visions for the company.
You know?
No... He didn't tell me that.
Okay. but-but maybe... what do I know?
Maybe I hear wrong.
Maybe-maybe she's
somebody that says these things
- and then changes her mind.
- Excuse me.
Okay.
Hey. honey.
What you doing?
Pulling into Dallas.
- I got a lunch meeting.
- Yeah?
Yeah. a lunch meeting or a job interview?
Sweetheart. when I
say today's not the day.
I really mean it. all right?
You got fired and you didn't tell me?
Well. number one. I
got fired on a riverbank
while you were playing den
mother to a cheerleading squad.
Number two. I don't talk about problems
till I have solutions.
So. when I find a solution.
you and I'll discuss the solution
and see if the problem's
solved. Is that okay?
Honey. it's not 2008.
I ain't trying to drink my problems away.
I'm gonna solve this.
I'm gonna solve it for you
and for me and for the kids.
You know. I've done a
lot of shitty things in my life.
I know. but... I've never broken my word.
So. I give you my word.
We're all gonna be better off for this.
So can you believe in that?
I give you my word and you'll believe it?
Believing in you is the one thing
that I have no trouble doing.
Well. I can think of a few more. honey.
but we'll talk about that later.
- I love you.
- All right. I love you. too. sweetheart.
And I forgot to mention
your son's being charged
with murder. but I'll fix that. too.
Well. god. you got anything else?
Just dump it the fuck down on me.
Just give it to me. all right?
Son of a...
That was low. god.
That was fucking dirty.
What we got here?
Surveillance footage.
Lawyer's en route.
Gonna request it anyway.
Might as well show it to her.
Let me guess. footage
from surveillance cameras?
Ma'am. before we speak.
you all should watch this.
This went well past the
point of defense of another.
Back the footage up
30 seconds. would you?
That's not relevant to
this specific complaint.
Everyone with a law degree
in the room. raise their hand.
It's just me?
Back it up and play it.
That's what I'll be showing a jury...
And they can decide how
real a threat this man posed
and what measure of force
should be applied to stop him.
I noticed. detective Miller...
you were involved in a shooting
with a man armed with a pipe wrench.
Okay.
You shot the man 11 times.
Why not shoot him in the leg?
Under that specific situation.
I couldn't guarantee a shot to the leg
would stop the assailant.
But you're trained
to make those quick
decisions. aren't you?
Cooper. how much use-of-force
training have you received?
None.
According to the autopsy...
All 11 rounds hit center mass.
meaning the first bullet likely killed him.
eliminating any threat
of continued violence.
yet you shot him ten more times.
Let me explain what will happen
if this department charges my client.
I will go to the family of this man
and file civil suit for wrongful
death times ten based on
this department's now established policy
of holding untrained citizens responsible
for knowing when a threat of
violence has been eliminated.
Then I will go through every
officer-involved shooting
in this county and file a class action suit
on behalf of the family members
of every suspect killed
in a similar fashion.
You getting my drift?
I will use your prosecution
to bankrupt this county
and every one of you.
And the more you prove your case.
the more you prove mine.
Stand up.
Is he being detained?
Not yet.
Go home. Cooper.
There's my card.
Never contact my client again.
Think real hard before
you charge the man
who saved the
22-year-old widow from rape
in a back alley with murder.
'Cause I have a pretty good
feeling a jury in this county
will find the man got
exactly what he deserved.
But...
if you do...
What's the saying you
guys use around here?
"Fuck with the bull and get the horn"?
It's a zero-sum game for me. gentlemen.
I am a life-ruiner.
You go after that kid for
saving his fiancée's life?
Ruin lives is exactly what I'm gonna do.
Starting with yours.
Why are y'all picking this fight?
Somebody tried to
rape my wife or yours?
- What would you do different?
- It ain't us.
Guy was a big pipeline supplier.
Suits don't like the message it sends
when they get beat to death in an alley.
I don't like the message
that we charge people
for beating up rapists either.
Take it up with the chief.
I plan to.
Hey.
I have seen a video of the event.
All right. walk me through it.
So. the perp had beat
Ariana unconscious
and was removing her
clothing when Cooper arrived.
Cooper pulled the man off and...
Well. your son beat the hell out of him.
Just give it to me straight. Rebecca.
What did the police do?
What are his chances?
It's too early to say.
If pd lists it as a justified homicide.
then this is done. Simple as that.
Can a county attorney find
any sympathy for a rapist
in a west Texas jury?
I would think it unlikely.
but the more strings you can pull
before that point. the better.
All right. listen. I'm gonna
be back by three o'clock.
I need to see you later. okay?
There's more to talk about than this.
I'm around.
Boy. your lawyer put
the fear of god in 'em.
They ain't seen the fear of god yet. Walt.
- Who's pushing for this?
- Don't know.
I'm heading to the
chief's office right now.
All right. well. I want to sit with him
and the county attorney this
afternoon. Walt. You got it?
- I'll tell 'em.
- Okay.
Yeah!
- Whoo! Like that. Yeah.
- Give us some more.
- Like that.
Yeah.
- Whoo! Like that.
- Like that.
- Just like that. yeah.
- Come on. baby.
Who are they?
High school kids.
We call 'em the future douches.
Come on. do the splits!
Okay. dweebs.
- Yeah.
- Hey. Hey.
What is that?
A cyborg.
Hey. what are you?
Are you a cheerleader?
No. she's on the football team.
No. she's a hobgoblin.
Hey. are you a linebacker?
- What's going on?
- Hey. which cheerleader's
your girlfriend?
Hey. how about y'all shut up?
Hey. why don't you make us?
Hey!
My god. you're hot.
You think that's cool?
Insulting our teammate? Insulting us?
What. you guys big.
grown-up boys now?
All cool on your dumb little bikes?
Cool enough to handle you.
You think so?
Okay. prove it. Whip it out.
Let's see it.
I bet mine's bigger.
You're rude little boys.
Girls like us don't date boys like you.
So. gawk away.
This is the closest you're ever gonna get.
Bye.
Have a shitty life.
All right. Let's pack it in for the day.
Tomorrow 9 A.M. in
the weight room to start.
Norris.
Yes. ma'am.
Need your kicks higher.
Okay. I'll work on it.
- How do you work on it?
- Stretching.
Standing up for your teammate
like that on day one. though.
I like that.
I don't hate all music.
Just the kind I don't like.
Yeah. I'm the same way. I think.
What kind of music do you like?
Just depends on my mood.
- You know Lainey Wilson?
- Yeah. I dig her.
Yeah. what about. Ella Langley?
- I don't know.
- It's awesome.
I didn't mean to run you off. I just...
Thought we should
have some ground rules.
Yeah. we should. but we
should both come up with them.
- I'm cool with that.
- Okay.
Can ferrets have baths?
I don't know. I've never tried.
I think that's a good place to start.
Could be a real shit show.
Welcome to my life.
All right. well. I guess
we're gonna bathe a ferret.
Freakin' a. we are.
All right.
Boo.
How was practice?
It was really hard.
Get in.
What do you think about me
giving dorm life another try?
Did you find a new roommate?
I worked things out with the old one.
I think.
Y'all are pretty different.
I know. but if we can get
the ferret smelling better.
then we have a chance.
I'm sweaty. mama.
- All grown up.
- Okay.
I'll Uber over later and I'll get my stuff.
- Okay. Have fun.
- I will. I love you.
I love you.
She can see you now.
Thank you.
Nathan. come on in. have a seat.
Got the keys to the kingdom right here.
The reason we couldn't find
anything on the computers is...
everything was in hard
copy in the basement.
It's gonna take a while to go through.
but at least now I know
where everything is.
I never thought of. monty as old-school.
No electronic files. everything on paper.
What would the reason
be for that. I-I wonder?
So. if there was a criminal investigation
or civil litigation. he
could destroy the evidence
without leaving an electronic trail.
And you were okay with this?
I understand getting
distance from liability.
but did I approve? No.
So what should we do?
Should we scan these
into the computer?
That's your decision.
Well. I'm asking your opinion.
I don't have one.
Well. the president of a
company needs to have opinions.
You understand what I'm asking?
Tommy said you might try
to make me interim president.
Well. Tommy is nothing if not shrewd.
So. I assume you coming
means you're accepting?
Quite the opposite.
I came here to offer my resignation.
Monty didn't design this
company to outlive him.
Read enough of those
files and you'll learn why.
He designed it to be sold.
Tommy can help you with that.
I can help you with that.
and I sure hope you'll
give us the chance.
For your sake.
For your family's sake.
Let us sell this thing...
Before it's the end of you. too.
We got six pumping
with a flow over 6.500.
We're set to go on seven.
and we got another 28 leases.
We hit on a pocket that
the whole world missed.
Could be 50 to 100 million barrels.
Where exactly is this?
I'll tell you where when we have a deal.
So. let me get this straight.
$44 million gets me 50% of the existing
- and 75 of all new production?
- Yeah.
Or you could farm it
back to us and go 60-40.
Where did you get the money to drill?
M-Tex covered the drilling.
So my deal's with m-Tex?
No. your deal's with me.
Okay. I'm... And I'm not
making any accusations.
But the term for that is
embezzlement. Tommy.
Even if I pay m-Tex back with interest.
and I understand the sinking ship
that m-Tex is becoming.
and you're right to grab a life raft. but...
I run a publicly traded company.
Anything we do is under the scrutiny
of our shareholders. the sec.
and every state and federal
regulatory agency in existence.
Now. the railroad commission. they...
May look the other way. but the ftc won't.
U.S. attorneys won't.
I can't even dabble in the gray. Tommy.
Now. you figure this out.
you bring her back to me all cleaned up
with all this mess behind it?
Maybe we can have a conversation.
Yeah. okay. Understood. Bob.
Well. I'm sorry to leave early. Bob.
but I'm on the clock.
I have no doubt.
Tommy.
You can just walk away from all this.
Let m-Tex absorb it. and you're clean.
Do that. I will make you a vice president
of production the next day.
Seven-figure base.
bonuses. stock options.
No more chasing your tail.
I appreciate that. Bob.
but I just got to know.
Know what?
If I got one more home run in me.
Hey. babe.
That's it. I mean. she is gone.
Fucking grown-up and
gone. with her nonbinary.
ferret-owning fucking new friend.
That's the job. ain't it. honey?
You get 'em grown. you get 'em gone.
The job sucks.
Now I got to drive back
to midland by myself
and wallow in it.
Well. just meet me at
alliance and fly with me.
- Can you still use the jet?
- Cami don't even know
about the fucking jet.
and I'm gonna use the
shit out of it till she does.
Well. what about my car?
I'll have it on a flatbed tomorrow.
I'll just drive.
Honey. we got a lot to talk about.
and none of it's good.
so meet me at the airport.
- Okay.
- All right.
Yes?
Hey. I need to see you.
When?
As soon as I can get there.
I'm in Dallas. but I'm on the way.
- Okay.
- All right.
I don't know. Tommy.
I don't know.
We tried this once before. and...
You didn't want me as a partner.
Plus I'm... I made a pretty
sizable investment with cami.
An investment you'll lose.
You seem so certain about that.
- Yeah. you want to know why?
- Yeah.
'Cause I've seen this a thousand times.
There's no comparable business to oil
except Las Vegas.
And what do they have in common?
The house always wins
'cause the house can afford to lose.
When BP's deep water horizon blew.
it dumped three million
barrels in the Gulf.
That company's fine.
When Piper Alpha blew. 1988.
killed 167 men. That company's fine.
Because they're too big to fail.
And now...
You're risking something
that they analyze for years.
On a hunch and a mandate
from a fucking insurance company.
Monty was a Blackjack player.
When he lost. he took a marker.
When he won. he paid a marker.
But monty's gone.
And now his wife's holding all your chips.
and she don't even
fucking know how to play.
Now. if there's gas
and if you can reach it at 30.000 feet
and if you can seal the well
without salt water invading
and if the pressures hold
and if you don't hit an
air pocket. who knows?
You're six miles under
the surface of the ocean.
And if you achieve all that.
now you need export
contracts with Europe.
a region wholly committed
to ridding dependence on lng.
Now you need no hurricanes.
no pressure valve
failures. no earthquakes.
no tectonic plate shifts.
and you're at the mercy
of underwater welders
and engineers and politicians
who fucking despise this industry.
and you need all this from a
person who never ran a company.
let alone an oil company.
and you don't need her
husband's $1.3 billion in debt
come calling on you.
That's a lot of ifs.
I'd say so.
But those are her ifs. What are your ifs?
I don't have ifs.
I got six Wells that are producing
between 250 and 500 barrels a day.
I got another 28 to work over
within a five-mile radius.
and I have exclusive
rights to drill new ones
any-fucking-where I please.
We are the house.
And in our little world we're too big to fail.
Now I grow the world.
I need you to honor the
original contract with Cooper.
and I need you to extend
an additional $18 million
for the next three Wells.
You'll recoup at 70%.
then it's 50-50 forever.
Your first check for just under $6 million
will arrive in less than a week.
and they don't stop coming.
This is what you asked me for.
and this is what I'm giving you.
$40 million?
Forty-four.
Interest on the m-Tex advance.
Just make it out to. m-Miller enterprises.
And the $18 million?
I need a name. Tommy.
Ctt oil exploration.
And cattle.
And cattle? Are we in
the cattle business. too?
No. I just hadn't formed an llc yet. so...
I needed something so stupid
nobody else would have it.
You're right. I may lose
everything with cami.
and I won't like it. but
I'm not gonna hold her responsible
because she doesn't
know what she's doing.
And I only partnered
with her because of you.
Because you know what you're doing.
So. if you lose this
and you try to fuck me in any way.
the thing you love the most.
that's the first thing I'll take.
What a great way to start a partnership.
Anything you lose with cami.
I'll make it back for you in three years.
Like the sound of that.
- Let's celebrate.
- I can't.
I got to go keep my son out of prison.
It's like I'm looking in a mirror.
except I'm skinny and I wear a hat.
I hoped that's what you were doing.
It's done. What about the contract?
I resigned. That's
what about the contract.
Nate. I could kiss you right now.
Please don't.
Get on your computer. form an llc.
Ctt oil exploration and cattle.
You're the treasurer. Open
an account and deposit this.
- And cattle?
- Look.
I'm running on fumes.
buddy. Doing the best I can.
Hey. baby.
I hope you had a better day than I did.
I'm sorry.
I know what you want out of life.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
What do I want?
You want every meal to be memorable.
You want every moment
to be an experience.
You want every night
to be a honeymoon.
And I think it's beautiful.
Why are you saying this?
I can't tell you right now.
honey. The day's not over yet.
Are you worried about losing your job?
I got another job.
What's the job?
Guess who I just got off the phone with.
Chief of staff at the hospital.
And everybody here failed to tell me
that that son of a bitch died at the er
from a fucking heart attack.
Would he have had a heart attack
if he hadn't gotten the
living shit beat out of him?
My back is to you for a reason. bud.
because you don't
make the decisions here.
Maybe he would've
died from a heart attack
raping my future daughter-in-law.
Did you ever think about that?
A widow with a seven-month-old.
And we're siding with a rapist.
We're not siding with anybody. Tommy.
All right? We're just trying to follow
the letter of the law. that's all.
Criminals can be victims. too. Tommy.
How old's your daughter. Devin?
Isn't she about to graduate?
I don't see how my
daughter's relevant to this.
I think everybody's
and so is your wife and my wife.
Any rights that piece of shit might've had.
he left at the back door of that bar.
Now. is there a man in this room
that would've done anything different
if you had come in and
caught somebody attacking
your wife or your kid?
Well. I'll tell you what I
would've done different.
The son of a bitch wouldn't have seen
the inside of the er with me.
It'd have been straight
to the fucking morgue
with that piece of shit.
Now what do you say?
How about only one person
got their life ruined today?
No telling how much therapy this girl is
gonna need once she heals
up from her broken nose
and her separated ribs or
concussion and all that shit.
I'll tell you what. if this
leaks out to the press.
who do you think the people of midland
and Odessa are gonna side with?
It ain't gonna be that bloated
son of a bitch with a toe tag.
I think it's gonna be that girl.
And this feels like a
situation where mayors
start firing police chiefs
and county attorneys don't get reelected.
So what should it be. CBS or abc?
I guess you're just gonna
have to tune in and find out.
Tommy.
No one's made a decision here yet.
Just trying to work it out. that's all.
Well. I've already
worked it out in my mind.
and I'm telling the
whole world my decision.
Y'all just go with the heart attack.
Cleans this whole thing up.
For everybody.
What about the victim's family?
That would be my family.
And that girl's family.
That's the only victim.
Maybe a criminal can
be a victim sometimes.
but not while they're
committing a fucking crime.
You're either one or you're the other.
Well...
Charges haven't been filed yet.
We're just assessing
the situation. that's all.
The situation's been
assessed. Don't y'all agree?
County's got no problem with it.
That means I got no problem with it.
Hey. honey.
Hi.
Let me see.
Well. it looks like you
gave as good as you got.
Gave it all I got.
I don't doubt that.
Where's Cooper?
He's mowing the lawn.
That's what I always do when I'm being
investigated for murder.
You think he's gonna be charged?
I think that's all behind us now.
It's gonna eat at him. though.
It's already eating at him.
How about you? Is it eating at you?
Did he get what he deserved?
I don't know.
But did I get what I deserved?
It's quite the night.
I swear. trouble finds
me like flies at a picnic.
Listen. son. I talked
to the county attorney.
This ain't going no further. okay?
They're right. though.
I went past defending
her to punishing him.
Cooper. look at me. Look at me.
Don't ever say that again.
Don't say it to Ariana.
don't say it to anybody. Ever.
He didn't value her life.
and now he don't have a life. Period.
That's all this is. And another thing.
get her out of that fucking bar.
Already done it.
All right.
I need you to come with me.
I can't leave her here.
Well. bring her. too.
- We got Miguel.
- Bring the kid.
the dog. the whole
bunch. I don't give a shit.
It's fine. come on.
Hey. Cooper. I need you to gen z me up
a group text and send
a pin to your well six.
Who do you want on it?
Nate. Rebecca and Dale.
your crew. boss and king...
What's that other kid?
- Br.
- Yeah.
And look up Cheyenne.
It's probably under "stripper."
There's a stripper
Jasmine. Harmony. destiny...
That's all for work.
I got it.
All right. well. tell 'em
all to meet me at the pin.
Tell Cheyenne to bring pop.
Sure glad I got my car washed today.
Well. that'll teach you to not tailgate. hon.
Well. I think most of y'all
know. my son's gathered up
all the leases around here.
About seven square miles of 'em.
So far. they've hit. Every one of 'em.
So I've negotiated a deal
with a company out of fort
worth to finance exploration
at a 50-50 split.
and they'll cover all the existing Wells.
Y'all know what that means?
We've got our own oil company.
And we're gonna drill
out this whole damn field.
All right? Now here's my proposal.
25% of the profits is
gonna be put in a pool
and distributed among all the employees.
Now let me introduce you to the board.
There's your president right there.
I'm senior vice president.
unless my son decides to fire me.
Nate's the treasurer.
Rebecca. chief operating
officer and chief counsel.
And Dale?
Yes. sir?
You're gonna head up exploration.
Yes. sir.
And. pop. you're gonna
oversee the drilling.
I can't climb that fucking ladder to a rig.
You don't have to climb a ladder. pop.
It's all computerized.
You just sit in a room
and control the drill with a joystick.
I don't know how to
work a joystick either.
Well. get Cheyenne to help you.
God knows she's had practice.
Hardy-har.
And. boss. you run the
crew. How's that sound?
Sounds fucking good to me. Tommy.
You boys in?
- I'm in.
- Yeah. me. too.
Dale?
- You don't even have to ask.
- All right. buddy.
'Cause it's been so much
fun up to this point. sure.
All right!
Now. Ariana. if you want
work. I can find it for you.
- Like what?
- Well. we need a secretary.
Do I look like anyone's secretary to you?
How about office manager?
How does it pay?
Son. you just got a glimpse
into your future right there.
This thing got a name?
Ctt oil exploration.
And cattle. unfortunately.
What are we doing with cattle?
Nothing. pop. it's just legal horseshit.
Don't worry about it.
So. what's ctt?
Cooper. Tommy. Thomas.
All right. So when do we start?
We already started. son.
All right.
Hey. baby.
I never noticed these horses.
I had horses as a kid.
Yeah?
You know. honey. the
time's coming when...
tragedy's gonna dominate our days.
Maybe it's me. maybe it's cancer.
Maybe my mind goes.
I wake up one morning
and I don't have a clue who you are.
Or. god forbid. maybe it's you.
Car wreck or whatever. you know.
But not today.
Today we win.
Baby. I win every day.
You do. too.
You just don't see it.
But it's there.
I mean. it's all around you.
Just got to take the time to notice.
Like now.
Like me...
walking upstairs to take a bath.
Nothing on but my birthday suit.
It's worth watching.
No.
You can't have today. bud.
Today is mine.